Guide to the Turkish Photography Collection 1910-1990 AD.MC.007
AbuDhabi
- A young male looking off camera in a light suit and dark tie, with a small rectangular mustache. Ottoman writing in on the front. Studio Phebus. 13.5 x 8.7 cm, 22 August 1927 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Mustaches; Ottoman Writing; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
- A young couple, female in a dark dress with design on the left chest and dark lipstick. Foto Can. 8.6 x 13.4 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Couple; Jewelry; Makeup; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
- Two females, one in a light dress, the other in dark, sitting next to a young male in a dark suit. 8.6 x 13.5 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Jewelry; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits; Women
- A bride standing in front of a mirror with flowers in her hands surrounded by four males in dark suits. 8.4 x 13.3 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Brides; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits; Wedding Ceremony; Wedding Veil
- A group of males with dark suits, with one female in a dark dress with white collar standing in the middle in front of a building. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Furnishings; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits; Women
- Three children, female child in a flower patterend dress, older male in a suit with design on pocket, young male in sailor outfit. 8.6 x 13.5 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Boys; Children; Girls; Maritime Outfit; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A mixed group of four seated females and two standing males in front of a large tree. 8.5 x 12.7 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Men; Parks; Photographic Prints; Trees; Women
- A group of four males in suits sitting on wooden chairs at a wooden table. 9.0 x 13.5 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Furnishings; Hats; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Suits
- A mixed group of males and females sitting on a couch and an Oriental carpet inside a house. 9.0 x 13.3 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Furnishings; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- A woman in a black dress seated in an ornate chair with a console table with flowers in the background. 8.8 x 11.2 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Flowers; Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Women
- A group of males standing and squatting in front of a single storey white stone building. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Children; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
- A group of eight females in winter coats, standing in the snow in front of a large bulding. 14.1 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Buildings; Coats; Girls; Photographic Prints; Snow
- A multi-generational family group of five, standing in front of a car on the side of a road. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Cars; Children; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Family; Photographic Prints
- A large family group gathered in front of some large flowers, young female in the middle is holding a small bouquet. 13.9 x 9.0, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Children; Family; Flowers; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
- A group of five women in dress with a small boy and girl standing on the sidewalk next to cars. 8.7 x 13.5 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Cars; Children; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Women
- A large group of young girls in school uniform seated on a small wooden dock. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Docks; Girls; Photographic Prints; Seas; Uniforms
- A group of three females of differing ages seated in one chair with a suitcase and radiator in the background. 8.5 x 13.6 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Girls; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Women
- A family group, female in a dark dress with a light collar and an intricate head wrap. 8.5 x 13.3 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Boys; Children; Family; Family Portraits; Head Covers; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A group of four men and one woman sitting in front of a wood paneled wall with type-writers on wooden desks. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Men; Offices; Photographic Prints; Suits; Typewriters; Women
- Two men in a marina drinking ayran out of small glass bottles, with boats and a large pier in the background. 9.0 x 12.2 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Boats; Docks; Drinking; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Men; Photographic Prints
- Seven women in bathing suits/bikinis at a resort with water and bungalows in the background. 8.9 x 13.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Bathing Suits; Boats; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Women
- Two males in military uniform in an armoured military vehicle with a mounted gun and mountains in the background. 8.7 x 12.7 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Cars; Guns; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Uniforms
- A woman in a bathing suit and hat, on a rustic pier, with boats in the background. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Bathing Suits; Boats; Docks; Hats; Photographic Prints; Women
- Three females and one male relaxing at the beach with a small wooden boat on a trailer. 9.2 x 11.4 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Bathing Suits; Beach; Boats; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- Men in military uniform seated in the grass with an even larger group of men in uniform in the background. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Uniforms
- Men gathered around a table with a single female seated at it. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Men; Photographic Prints; Suits; Women
- A large family group gathered around a bed, a small girl with a light bow in her hair is in focus in the foreground. 7.2 x 13.2 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Children; Family; Head Covers; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- Five females seated on wooden stools behind wodden benches, female in the middle is wearing a light bucket hat. 9.0 x 14.1 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Clocks & Watches; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Fashion Accessories; Hats; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Women
- Four women, three standing, one squatting on a slabbed walk-way in front of a body of water and some trees. 8.9 x 11.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
- An older male with a young male seated on his lap and a standing male and female. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Children; Men; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants; Women
- Two men with pencil mustaches, at a table, drinking ayran from small glass bottles. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Cigarettes; Drinking; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants
- Two males in suits standing on a cliff side with the water in the background next to a stone wall. 9.2 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Beach; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
- Men and women seated around a bride with a tiara and veil on. 8.5 x 13.3 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Brides; Children; Men; Photographic Prints; Wedding Ceremony; Wedding Veil; Women
- Two females sitting in front of an open window, one is eating off a small plate. 9.2 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Cigarettes; Eating; Makeup; Party; Photographic Prints; Smoking
- Two females, with a male dressed in a suit with bottles on a table. 8.8 x 13.1 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Alcohol; Drinking; Jewelry; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Suits; Women
- Young males in suits, standing in front of a fountain hold a board with 224 on it, with buildings in the background. 9.0 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Boys; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools; Suits
- Men and women seated at a table with a checkered table cloth drinking out of wine glasses. 8.9 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Cigarettes; Drinking; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Smoking; Suits; Women
- Seven young girls in costumes with vests and head-dresses on. 8.5 x 13.5 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Costumes; Dancing; Girls; Photographic Prints; Schools; Traditional Dress
- Young men in sports kits with numbers pinned to their shirts all starting with 2[..]. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Boys; Men; Photographic Prints; Sports
- Four men in a small white wooden boat on the water. 8.9 x 13.7 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Boats; Men; Photographic Prints
- A group of males and females gathered around a Jeep vehicle with a man in military uniform sitting on the hood. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Cars; Children; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Women
- A man with a saz (long necked string instrument), in front of a wall with pictures of women in various stages of undress. 9.1 x 13.5 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Men; Musical Instruments; Naked; Photographic Prints; Women
- Small, mixed group, seated on chairs around a table outside, two males are in military uniform. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Alcohol; Gardens; Girls; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Women
- Mixed males and females, bride in the center of a group in a white dress and a veil. 8.4 x 13.2 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Brides; Family; Grooms; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Wedding Ceremony; Wedding Veil
- A mixed family group of nine, in front of some patterend curtains. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Children; Family; Head Covers; Military; Photographic Prints; Uniforms
- A group of men in traditional dresses with a man playing a large white drum on the streets. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Dancing; Men; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; Streets; Traditional Dress
- A group of five women seated on a low stone wall, second from left has a young child on her lap. 9.0 x 12.1 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Bathing Suits; Children; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Women
- Couples of varying ages dancing at an outdoor event with ballons, streamers and hanging lights. 9.0 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Children; Couple; Dancing; Men; Party; Women
- Men and women, some in lab coats standing outside buildings with military vehicle parked outside. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Cars; Doctors; Men; Military; Nurses; Photographic Prints; Women
- A group of males and females seated around a large wooden desk, some with photo ID badges pinned to their shirts. 9.2 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Men; Offices; Photographic Prints; Women
- Two males in jackets, with an older seated covered woman in front of a television. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Head Covers; Men; Photographic Prints; Televisions; Women
- A group of men in suits, with large trees in the background. Older male on the left is holding a young child. 8.7 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Children; Cigarettes; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Men; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Suits
- A group of males in sports uniforms, with some men in military uniform. Male squatting on the far right has a football in his hands. Foto Bahri. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Military; Photographic Prints; Sports; Uniforms
- A group of men in football uniforms on a football pitch with their coach. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Men; Photographic Prints; Sports; Uniforms
- A family group seated on a balcony. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Children; Cigarettes; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- An older male wearing a costume in satin and a head-dress, from a play. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Costumes; Men; Performance Play; Studio Photography
- Three males standing in front of palm trees, male in the middle has a mustache. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Men; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Trees
- A mixed group of males and females seated at cafe tables on a gravel patio. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Cameras; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Women
- A male in a dark suit sitting at a table writing, female in white dress standing at the desk with flower arrangements in the background. 9.2 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Flowers; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- Four females sitting on a flower patterend couch drinking out of small wine glasses. 8.5 x 13.5 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Drinking; Photographic Prints; Women
- Postcard of Constantinople and the Golden Horn. Constantinople - Corne d'Or et Stamboul. 8.7 x 13.6 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Beyazit Tower; Constantinople; Postcards; Suleymaniye Mosque; The Golden Horn
- Postcard of Constantinople. Constantinople - Vue générale des Eaux-Douces d'Europe. 8.8 x 13.4 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Constantinople; Postcards; The Golden Horn
- Postcard of Constantinople. Constantinople - Kiosk du Sultan aux eaux douces d'Asie. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Bosphorous; Constantinople; Kucuksu Palace; Postcards
- Postcard of Istanbul. Istanbul manzarai umumiyesi. 9.1 x 14.2 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Bosphorous; Galata Bridge; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; The Golden Horn
- Postcard of a train station in Algeria. 263 ALGER - La Route de Malakoff et la Gare de Bab-el-Oued. 8.7 x 13.7 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Algiers, Algeria; Postcards; Seas; Trains
- Postcard of Constantinople. Constantinople - Mosquee Validé. Sultan Valide Mosque aka the New Mosque (Yeni Cami). 8.7 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Constantinople; Mosques; New Mosque; Postcards; Steamboats; Yeni Cami
- Postcard of a boat on the Bosphorous in front of Rumeli Hisari Fortress. Le Bosphore devant Roumeli-Hissar. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Bosphorous; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Rumelihisari
- Postcard of the Golden Horn. 35 Istanbul Haliç - La Corne d'Or. 8.8 x 14.1 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Beyazit Tower; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Suleymaniye Mosque; The Golden Horn
- Postcard of a view of Rumelihisari and the Bosphorus. Vue des châteaux et des Eaux douces d'Asie au Bosphore. 8.7 x 13.5 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Postcard of the Turkish Cemetery in Scutari (Uskudar). Cimetière turc a Scutari. 8.3 x 13.7 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Cemetery; Constantinople; Postcards; Uskudar, Turkey
- Postcard of the port of Constantinople. Constantinople - Vue Panoramique du Port. 8.7 x 13.4 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Bosphorous; Constantinople; The Golden Horn
- Postcard of Bebek on the Bosphorous. Constantinople - Vue de Bébek Bosphore. 8.7 x 13.5 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Bebek, Besiktas, Turkey; Boats; Bosphorous; Rumelihisari; Steamboats
- Postcard of the Suleymaniye Mosque and the Golden Horn. 152 Istanbul, Suleymaniye Camii ve Haliç - Mosq. Suleimaniye et la Corne d'Or. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Suleymaniye Mosque; The Golden Horn
- Postcard of people on a ferris wheel with a Turkish flag in the background. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Entertainment; Flags; Photographic Prints; Postcards
- Postcard of the Galata Bridge in Istanbul. Istanbul, Galata Köprüsü 192 - Le Pont. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Galata Bridge; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; The Golden Horn; Yeni Cami
- Postcard of Sultan Ahmed Mosque (aka The Blue Mosque) and the Hippodrome. Mosquée de Sultan Ahmed et L'Hippodrome. 8.9 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Blue Mosque; Constantinople; Hippodrome of Constantinople; Ottoman Writing; Postcards
- Postcard of Yuksek-Kaldirim, a neighborhood in Istanbul. Salute de Constantinople - Yuksek-Kaldérim (neighborhood). 13.8 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Constantinople; Galata Tower; Postcards; Yuksek Kaldirim, Istanbul, Turkey
- Postcard of small boats on canals. Constantinople - Vue des Eaux-Douces d'Asie. 8.6 x 1.5 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Boats; Constantinople; Postcards
- Postcard of the Dolma Bache Palace. Constantinople - Palais de Dolma Bagtche. 8.5 x 13.3 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Bosphorous; Constantinople; Dolmabahce Palace; Postcards
- Postcard of boats in the port of Constantinople. Constantinople - Port de Constantinople. 8.6 x 13.7 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Boats; Constantinople; Ports; Postcards
- Postcard of the interior of the Grand Bazaar. Constantinople - Intérieur du Grand Bazar. 8.7 x 13.7 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Constantinople; Grand Bazaar; Postcards; Shopkeepers
- Postcard of the War Ministry Square/entrance of Istanbul University. Constantinople - Place du Séraskérat. 8.6 x 13.6 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Beyazit Tower; Constantinople; Istanbul University; Postcards
- Postcard of Uskudar, Istanbul and the Bosphorous. Istanbul. Vue de Scutari au Bosphore. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Bosphorous; Cihangir, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Istanbul, Turkey; Maiden's Tower; Postcards; Uskudar, Turkey
- Postcard of the Ortakoy Mosque. Mosque of Ortakeuï Constantinople. 8.7 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Bosphorous; Constantinople; Ortakoy Mosque; Postcards
- Postcard of the Ministry of War complex, now the entrance to Istanbul University. Constantinople - Minstére de la Guerre. 9.2 x 13.2 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Postcard of the Turkish Cemetery in Uskudar. Constantinople - Cimetiére turc a Scutari. 8.6 x 13.6 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Postcard of the Sunnet bridge in Kagithane. Constantinople. Eaux douces d'Europe. 8.6 x 13.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Boats; Constantinople; Kagithane, Istanbul, Turkey; Parks; Postcards
- Postcard of the abolution fountain at the Yeni-Cami (New Mosque). Constantinople - Fountaine d'Ablutions a Jéni-Djami. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Constantinople; Head Covers; New Mosque; Postcards; Yeni Cami
- Postcard of the Eyup Cemetery and the Golden Horn. Constantinople - Cimetiére d'Eyoub et La Corne d'Or. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Cemetery; Constantinople; Eyup, Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; The Golden Horn
- Postcard of the Ortakoy Mosque. Salut de Constantinople - Mosquée Validé a Ortakeuy - Bosphore. 9.0 x 13.7 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Boats; Bosphorous; Constantinople; Mosques; Ortakoy Mosque; Postcards
- Postcard of the Column of Constantine (aka the Burnt Stone)., Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Column of Constantine; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- Postcard. Constantinople. Derwiches Tourneurs - Whirling Dervishes gathered on a large carpet with instruments., undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Constantinople; Dervishes; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- Two men sitting in a cemetery with large trees in the background., undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Cemetery; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- Postcard. Constantinople - Mosquée du Sultan Ahmed et l'Hippodrome - The Mosque of Sultan Ahmed and the Hippodrome in Constantinople., undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Blue Mosque; Constantinople; Hippodrome of Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey
- 102 Constantinople - Int. de Ste. Sophia - Close up of the Hagia Sophia with large Ali medallion, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Constantinople; Hagia Sophia; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- Constantinople - Stamboul au coucher du soleil - Bosphorous at sunset with Constantinople in the background., undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Beyazit Tower; Bosphorous; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Suleymaniye Mosque; The Golden Horn
- Constantinople - Vue Panoramique de la Mosquée Suleymanie - Panoramic view of the Suleymanie Mosque in Constantinople., undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Suleymaniye Mosque; The Golden Horn
- 123 A Turkish barber shop in Constantinople Turkey - Overpainted colored postcard, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- Overpainted colored postcard of Constantinople. Arsenal Maritime - Imperial Arsenal or Tersâne-i Âmire was the main base and naval shipyard. Eyoub - Eyüp, neighborhood in Istanbul. Kassim Pacha - Neighborhood in Istanbul, 19 November 1947 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Constantinople; Eyup, Istanbul, Turkey; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; The Golden Horn
- Postcard. Jerusalem - Busy David Street - David Street in Jerusalem., undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Jerusalem; Postcards
- 52 Damas - La Forteresse - The Fortress/Citadel of Damascus, Syria, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Damascus, Syria; Postcards
- Postcard. Covered women walking along a cobbled stone street with tall stone buildings in the background., undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Postcards; Women
- 6240 Scénes et Types - Group de Mauresques - Postcard of three Moorish women in traditional dress., undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Postcards; The Moors; Women
- Port Said - Main Street - Overpainted colored postcard. Main Street of Port Said, shops selling cigarettes., undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Port Said, Egypt; Postcards; Shopkeepers
- Môise springs at Suez - Môise Springs at Suez in Egypt. Date palms, people carrying water. Printed for Ar[...]ugheti Bros. Suez., undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Postcards; Suez, Egypt; Trees
- 18 Alexandria - Cherif Pacha Street - Postcard of Sherif Pasha Street in Alexandria, Egypt with horse drawn carriages with buildings in the background., undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Alexandria, Egypt; Postcards
- 17 Alexandria - Mosque Attarine Street - Postcard of Attarine mosque Street in Alexandria, Egypt, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Alexandria, Egypt; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Streets
- Two men kneeling to pray with a camel in front of the Nile and the Pyramids of Giza., undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Alexandria, Egypt; Camels; Nile River; Postcards; Pyramids of Giza
- 69 Port Said - General View Town and Canal - General view of the town and canal of Port Said, Egypt., undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Port Said, Egypt; Postcards
- Postcard. Bedouin men and camels in the desert with a town in the background. Arabic writing in red ink., undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Camels; Postcards
- 64 Port Said - The Harbour - Postcard. Three large ships in the harbour of Port Said, Egypt., undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Port Said, Egypt; Ports; Postcards
- Caravan of camels walking along a tree lined road, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Camels; Postcards; Trees; Women
- Three women in traditional dress with intricate head wraps., undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Postcards; Traditional Dress; Women
- 1014 Femmes Arabes - Two Arab females sitting and standing in front of a intricately carved doorway., undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
- 390 Belle Fatma - J. Geiser, Alger - A female in traditional dress. Algeria, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Algeria; Algiers, Algeria; Postcards; Traditional Dress; Women
- 6370 Scénes et Types - Femme Arabe voilée, Costume de Ville, Edition Sion-Bismuth, 9, Avenue de France, Tunis - A female with a dark face cover and light dress., undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Postcards; Traditional Dress; Tunis, Tunisia; Women
- Femme indigéne ouled nail - A female holding dates over her head and date palms in the background., 1930 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Postcards; Traditional Dress; Trees; Women
- 35. - Scénes et Types - Fillettes Kabyles - Two barefoot females standing in front of some crude houses., undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Girls; Postcards; Traditional Dress
- Ghardaia - Vue d'ensemble - A group of camels, mostly seated in front of a small hill-top town. Ghardaïa is the capital city of Ghardaïa Province, Algeria., undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Algeria; Camels; Postcards
- 826 Mauresque - A Moorish female covered in a white cloak with a dark dress underneath standing next to a body of water., undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Postcards; The Moors; Traditional Dress; Women
- 1093 Scénes et Types - La Belle Fatma, Costume de femme Arabe riche - A female dress in traditional dress., undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Furnishings; Postcards; Traditional Dress; Women
- Two young females on a roof top looking out over Algiers., undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Algiers, Algeria; Girls; Postcards